<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="6FC2B3E7-67AD-4FEB-B35E-19203ADD6156">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20150327" date="2015-03-27 15:51:47 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Michelle McBeth</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I&#x2019;ve had several websites over the years. Most have been filled with silliness or rants that would mean nothing to people who didn&#x2019;t know me personally. This is my first attempt at a more professional website. Now that I am about to be a published author, I fear the responsibility that comes with that to my fans. I&#x2019;m not on Facebook, something I declare with pride, and I don&#x2019;t have a twitter account. Yet. I&#x2019;m hoping to avoid it, but who knows.&#xD;&#xD;I don&#x2019;t consider myself a writer. Even though I&#x2019;m now published, I still don&#x2019;t consider myself a writer. When people ask what I do, I still say: Electrical Engineer. Referring to myself as an author is such a foreign concept to me. It was years before I would call myself an actor. I don&#x2019;t get paid for it, but I am an actor. I&#x2019;m also a baker, and a crafter, and most recently, a voiceover artist.&#xD;&#xD;Not that I don&#x2019;t enjoy writing. I enjoy it very much. Writing the first draft of my third book during Nanowrimo was a blast. The words flew fast and furious. Conflict presented itself at every turn. Writing it was FUN. I discovered things about my characters that I never realized before.&#xD;&#xD;When I was writing the first book, by the end of it I was bored with Adelaide. I thought there were other characters in the book who would have much more interesting stories. One of those characters was Doctor Lancing, and I realized that telling his story would serve several purposes. For one, I always think it&#x2019;s more interesting when you have a chance to get to know the villain, and perhaps even sympathize with him or her. Then it also gave me a chance to go into the history of the laboratory. Why it was so restrictive, what things had happened in the beginning, lessons they learned, to enforce the rules they did. It forced me to work out my time travel canon even tighter. &#xD;&#xD;I almost wrote the third book about Daphne, but the overall plot I had in mind would not have worked with her. But given things that happened, I had a chance to rediscover and develop Adelaide&#x2019;s character even more than in the first book. And I loved doing it. Does that make me a writer? I guess so. So here begins a new chapter of life.&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, December 13, 2014&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="13_The_Beginning_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="266px" height="200px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The Beginning</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
