<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="6FC2B3E7-67AD-4FEB-B35E-19203ADD6156">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20170319" date="2017-03-19 15:02:23 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Michelle McBeth</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>To the left is a snapshot from The Washington Post online newspaper the other day. See that picture with the pope? That&#x2019;s what they ran on the front page with that headline about sharks. If you clicked on it, the article was actually about the sharks, but I found the mistake amusing. The appalling thing is the regularity with which these sorts of mistakes happen. In The Washington Post. A national newspaper.&#xD;&#xD;You paying attention Bezos? The other thing that has started to annoy me about Wapo articles is the number of times you&#x2019;ll go to read an article and in the middle of it are snapshots of what people on twitter are saying about something that happened. Is this what qualifies as journalism now? I went on twitter and copied the most liked comments for a specific hashtag? If I wanted to read twitter comments, I would be on the twitter. I don&#x2019;t need you to do it for me, &#x201C;journalist&#x201D;.&#xD;&#xD;Why do I get the impression that this is actually a decree that came down from up high? I could totally imagine Bezos saying to the top editors (or whatever equivalent power structure), &#x201C;We need to incorporate more social media in our newspaper!&#x201D; Or whatever management buzzwordy way he would say it. Slowly, Wapo will transform itself from an actual newspaper to the facebook of journalism, and we&#x2019;ll be reading stories about what&#x2019;s for sale on Amazon that day. I fear the future. Even if I shop on Amazon almost every day. &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, February 21, 2016&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Bloopers</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
