<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="6FC2B3E7-67AD-4FEB-B35E-19203ADD6156">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20170319" date="2017-03-19 15:02:20 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Michelle McBeth</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>I&#x2019;m a bad author that hasn&#x2019;t written to her blog in...apparently 6 weeks. But I had a project I&#x2019;ve been working on, that I wanted to post about!&#xD;&#xD;A few weeks ago I was cast as the ghost in Port City Playhouse&#x2019;s production of &#x201C;Shining City&#x201D; by Connor McPherson. It&#x2019;s a non-speaking role and most of my acting is through pictures that will be displayed, but I will appear on stage briefly, as the ghost.&#xD;&#xD;The director of the show was thinking it would be neat if they could find a way to get my eyes to glow red, and turns to me and says: Well you&#x2019;re an electrical engineer, can you find a way to make that happen?&#xD;&#xD;Of course! A couple of ping pong balls, felt, glue, high intensity LEDs and basic electronics later and I&#x2019;ve got a couple of working prototype eyes. I took them in to get a feel for which style the director liked better, then set to work putting them both into a more permanent arrangement with an on/off switch.&#xD;&#xD;So a few night ago I&#x2019;ve finally got the thing soldered together and am getting ready to cover the solder joints with heat shrink tubing to smooth them out and make me less prone to shorting something out with my wet hair (part of the costume). I don&#x2019;t have a heat gun at home, but Sean suggests using the soldering iron held close to the tube but not touching. It&#x2019;s working, but very very slowly, and I&#x2019;m impatient. So next he suggests holding a lighter up to the tube to make faster work of shrinking them.&#xD;&#xD;Great idea! Except that a slice of ping pong ball that&#x2019;s been slathered with glue and lined with felt is highly flammable.&#xD;&#xD;Well, I wasn&#x2019;t liking how that LED was seated anyway, so now I have a valid reason to re-do that eye. Take two; I&#x2019;m being patient and using the soldering iron for the joints near the eyeballs, at short intervals.&#xD;&#xD;The final product is feeling much better. The LEDs are solidly mounted and not likely to be shifting around on me. The wiring is cleaner. There will probably be some color changes once we figure out if I&#x2019;m wearing these with my glasses or not. But on the whole, it&#x2019;s done! Enjoy &lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/FA359BF4-DFA6-4496-A8A2-8BCF751B49B8"&gt;pictures&lt;/a&gt;!&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, February 16, 2015&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="16_Glowing_Eyes_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="212px" height="218px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Glowing Eyes</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
