<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog</link>
    <description></description>
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Any Cake</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2018/1/21_Not_Just_Any_Cake.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6920d019-72ee-4cff-ad97-71c16e2fb732</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 09:44:50 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;First, let me say that in my years of baking I have never found a cake recipe that I liked enough to replace the easiness and taste of Betty Crocker moist cake mixes. If I had more time, I might have made my own icing, but Duncan Hines cans are great in a pinch. Or really, at any point. Some things just aren&#x2019;t worth the effort for the return. This is coming from the woman who makes her own vanilla, and once made her own Amaretto but lamented the fact that she had no way of making her own almond extract to use.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My first son turned two years old a week ago. He&#x2019;s not quite at the point where he could tell us what he wanted his birthday to be, so we just decided on a generic &#x201C;Space&#x201D; theme. My husband came up with the brilliant idea of having a rocket ship cake. I think he expected me to come up with something like a rocket ship drawn with icing on a sheet cake, but that&#x2019;s for wimps and moms who have no time (like me). Besides, who hasn&#x2019;t wanted to take on the challenge of a three dimensional cake! And what better object to try it out on but rocket ship!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I pulled out some graph paper and drew myself a rocket ship, knowing that cake layers tend to rise to about 2 inches. Each square represented one inch, and I wanted something about 12 inches high. 6 layers, or 3 small layered cakes. The math wasn&#x2019;t working out with the diameters I needed for me to be able to cut these out of a 9x13 pan, so I found some smaller cake pans online and Amazoned them to myself next-day.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you search for how to bake level cakes online, the prevailing method seems to be shredding an old towel into strips, soaking them in cold water and tying them around your cake pan. It sort of worked for me. It&#x2019;s hard to tell without a control cake how much it helped.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I used my diagram to trim the 6 small round cake down to proper size and shape and started assembly. The very bottom of the cake consisted of one layer of flames, and one layer made of the rocket nozzle and the very bottom of the ship. I started out with a base of orangish red frosting, then added yellow streaks that I wiggled in to mix with the red a little (my father&#x2019;s idea). I then cut bamboo skewers down to the height of the two layers plus some frosting and 3 of those into the cake. I put a cake round that was also trimmed down and covered with foil on top of the skewers to help support the additional weight of the cake.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since the cake was still pretty fragile, I decided it made sense to assemble and ice the layers individually. Shortly after placing the second layer on top of the first, it toppled off. I think this was the first time I&#x2019;ve had to bring out a level to help with baking. The first layer was a bit tilted, so re-inserted the skewers to try and even them out a little. It helped a little, but so did the fact that in its topple over, the second layer also became uneven.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;My husband made the fins for me out of foam board, so my father suggested sticking toothpicks into those to help them hold the cake upright better. Genius! Who knew he was so good at cake baking? With the 2nd layer back on and oriented so the two tilts would cancel each other out, it was much more stable. The fins easily stuck in and provided even more reassurance that the whole thing wouldn&#x2019;t fall apart before anyone even saw it. More skewers and another cake round and the third layer went on without any issues!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Final touches included Sheffield&#x2019;s name (shortened to his nickname Sheffy for space reasons) and details like the windows. I rounded the whole thing out with planetary-looking cupcakes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When it cake time sing happy birthday, I put sparkler candles I had found into the bottom layer to try and simulate the rocket fire. Unfortunately, sparkler candles don&#x2019;t seem to spark unless they&#x2019;re upright. Oh well, it still looked cool and tasted awesome! Check out the &lt;a href="../My_Albums/Pages/Rocketship_Cake.html"&gt;album&lt;/a&gt; for pictures.</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2018/1/21_Not_Just_Any_Cake.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short story news</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/10/14_Short_story_news.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f3c3e6e-45ea-4fd0-9419-c4c6212cd3f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 09:52:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;Two bits of exciting news from the short story front. Firstly, my short story &#x201C;Fire Drill in Motherhood&#x201D; was selected for inclusion in the Virginia Writers Club&#x2019;s Centennial Anthology! It&#x2019;s a story about a woman who unexpectedly gives birth to a dragon instead of a human baby, and the resulting adventures in trying to raise such a child.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Another short story, &#x201C;The Usual&#x201D;, won my local chapter Golden Nib contest and is a finalist for the statewide contest, also through the Virginia Writers Club. It&#x2019;s about an unusual usual customer at a coffee house. Winners announced in November!</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/10/14_Short_story_news.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Scout Results</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/8/6_Kindle_Scout_Results.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc36a7a-c1c7-4025-9e81-fa66ace647ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2017 07:50:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;So I didn&#x2019;t win again, but I got a fair amount out of my campaign. For one thing, I did get a few people interested enough in my series to buy my first book. Here&#x2019;s hoping for some good reviews.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m pleased that I wasn&#x2019;t immediately rejected. Last time I got my no-thank-you notice in about three days. This time it was almost two weeks. I&#x2019;d like to think that they were seriously considering it and not just all on vacation. Since I&#x2019;ll never know for sure, I choose to believe the former.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I got about three times the page hits of my first campaign and an overwhelming 92% of those were people who simply found my book on KS and checked it out. Only 8% were people I sent the direct link to, begging for votes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As I suspected, by biggest hits were the last few days of my campaign. That seems to be the case with the hot &amp;amp; trending list as well-books that are about to end their campaigns are the majority of the list. It makes sense, since you only get three votes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I can&#x2019;t bring myself to be too disappointed. I&#x2019;m apparently not the target audience of most scouters, and to be honest, some of the books that get selected look pretty crappy. I understand KS does put you through a round or two of professional editing, but I guess if you&#x2019;re starting from 50 Shades, it&#x2019;s hard to improve to Scarlet Letter.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Oh well! Look for &#x201C;The Lunar Conspiracy&#x201D; in late August, 2017!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/8/6_Kindle_Scout_Results.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Panel</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/7/23_Author_Panel.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b76b8acd-666e-4906-a82b-d1491e95427b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 08:48:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>A few weeks ago I participated in an author panel hosted by the Northern Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club about &#x201C;Pathways to Publishing&#x201D;. See me on the right there? I&#x2019;m sitting next to several authors who have been published through the traditional route.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I was a little nervous since this is the first panel of this type I&#x2019;ve ever participated in, but it went well. I got a few laughs. We had a bigger audience than we had anticipated, and many people came up after to tell us how informative it had been. It was also interesting for me to sit up there and listen to authors who have gone the traditional route talk about the pros and cons. Some of the authors have gone both routes. It seems like the biggest comment on the differences is that self-publishing just means a lot more work on your part.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I had fun, and the club got a few new members and I hope we inspired some people to take the plunge and work on getting that book they&#x2019;ve had sitting around on their laptop for years finally published! If you&#x2019;re a writer in Norther Virginia or just Virginia, take a look at the websites for the Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club and our local chapter. They host lots of fun and informative events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.virginiawritersclub.org/"&gt;http://www.virginiawritersclub.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Northern Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://northernvirginiawriters.org/"&gt;http://northernvirginiawriters.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/7/23_Author_Panel.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Scout Take 2</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/6/24_Kindle_Scout_Take_2.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b947b18-73c1-4ecf-9327-b4fba1161d8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 07:24:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;Although &#x201C;The Sphere&#x201D; wasn&#x2019;t selected for publication by Kindle Scout, I am not discouraged by the idea of trying again. For one thing, my writing has improved greatly. For another, I now have three books in my series. Even if &#x201C;The Lunar Conspiracy&#x201D; isn&#x2019;t chosen either, I expect I&#x2019;ll see an uptick in sales from people who read the excerpt and are intrigued enough to go look at the first two books. And if I&#x2019;m not chosen, I can still publish on my own. Seems like a win-win.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A number of things have changed since my first try at Kindle Scout. For one thing, Amazon now provides you with daily page hits, so you can see how your book is doing. On day one, 326 people looked at my book. Unfortunately, they don&#x2019;t tell you how many of those people nominated your book. Bear in mind though, I haven&#x2019;t even started my social media push. Those are overwhelmingly people who were already on Kindle Scout, saw my book and decided to take a look at it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is one of the reasons why a good cover is so important. It&#x2019;s shallow, but the adage is true: People judge a book by its cover. So those books on Scout that are very obviously some clip art and basic fonts thrown onto a picture the author took themselves? I admit, I don&#x2019;t bother looking at them. I might be missing out on an awesome book, but it shows a lack of effort I just can&#x2019;t get past. Same thing if there are typos on the campaign page; of which I pray I don&#x2019;t have any.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As a scouter, there is also an advantage to waiting to nominate a book until it is close to ending. I&#x2019;d guess on average amazon adds five books a day, which means every day an average of five books are removed and weighed for publication. Every day you could nominate three out of those five books and possibly get three free books a day out of it! I haven&#x2019;t tested this theory, but it seems possible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And this is all free publicity for Amazon. They&#x2019;re making out big time with increased traffic to their websites and books they publish, or even books that end up self-publishing later. Amazon will now send an email to everyone who nominated your book when you publish it (if outside of Scout). It seems like a really sweet thing of them to do, until you realize that the majority of the proceeds from those sales goes directly to them. It&#x2019;s a pretty brilliant if shallow business model.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Judging from the books that tend to end up on the &#x201C;hot and trending&#x201D; list, it&#x2019;s clear my next book needs to be about a hot teenage vampire that falls in love with a hot teenage werewolf and has a love child that turns into a hot sorceress who travels through time seducing really hot young versions of famous men. The cover needs to feature at least two of these hot people showing lots of skin and contemplative faces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m copyrighting that idea, so no one better steal it!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/6/24_Kindle_Scout_Take_2.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
