<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog</link>
    <description></description>
    <item>
      <title>Gaithersburg</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/3/26_Gaithersburg.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58242a3f-2d08-4962-93a9-b1e0bfc6a5cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 08:14:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Yesterday was the Gaithersburg Book Festival. I was really pleased to get a spot again this year since it went so well for me last year. Even with the horrid weather and an infant in tow, it was a good time. I met some very nice people and got a few questions that really challenged me. I also have to thank my mother-in-law (back there with Sheffield) for helping out yesterday, and my husband (taking the selfie) for his awesome sales work. Though the tactic of yelling &#x201C;Time Travel&#x201D; at people walking by seemed to startle them more than get them to stop at the table.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On the right there is the concept of the cover for book number 3 in The Sphere Saga, tentatively titled &#x201C;The Lunar Conspiracy&#x201D;. Since so many people purchased copies of my books yesterday, I&#x2019;m going to extend the character name contest out a few more months. So if you read one of my books and &lt;a href="Entries/2015/12/19_Book_Contest%21.html"&gt;write a review&lt;/a&gt; before September, let me know!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/3/26_Gaithersburg.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloopers</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/2/21_Bloopers.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82a5e2d9-7bfd-4929-a894-0cffe28d4d61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 09:15:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>To the left is a snapshot from The Washington Post online newspaper the other day. See that picture with the pope? That&#x2019;s what they ran on the front page with that headline about sharks. If you clicked on it, the article was actually about the sharks, but I found the mistake amusing. The appalling thing is the regularity with which these sorts of mistakes happen. In The Washington Post. A national newspaper.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You paying attention Bezos? The other thing that has started to annoy me about Wapo articles is the number of times you&#x2019;ll go to read an article and in the middle of it are snapshots of what people on twitter are saying about something that happened. Is this what qualifies as journalism now? I went on twitter and copied the most liked comments for a specific hashtag? If I wanted to read twitter comments, I would be on the twitter. I don&#x2019;t need you to do it for me, &#x201C;journalist&#x201D;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Why do I get the impression that this is actually a decree that came down from up high? I could totally imagine Bezos saying to the top editors (or whatever equivalent power structure), &#x201C;We need to incorporate more social media in our newspaper!&#x201D; Or whatever management buzzwordy way he would say it. Slowly, Wapo will transform itself from an actual newspaper to the facebook of journalism, and we&#x2019;ll be reading stories about what&#x2019;s for sale on Amazon that day. I fear the future. Even if I shop on Amazon almost every day. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/2/21_Bloopers.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why didn&#x2019;t I pay more attention in school?</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/2/5_Why_didnt_I_pay_more_attention_in_school.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f58b98fc-41f4-49bf-9297-41f2be5c6e04</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 5 Feb 2016 08:31:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>The rough thing about writing science fiction is that it involves a lot of science along with the fiction.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I realize that sounds like an obvious statement, but think about what that actually means. If I want to be the type of author I&#x2019;d respect, it means lots and lots of research.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I&#x2019;m working on a short story that involves me understanding some amount of chemistry. I took chemistry in high school. I mostly coasted through on projects and extra credit. I got the basic concepts, but I never really paid them much attention.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now that I&#x2019;ve been looking into it again, I think I could have liked chemistry if I&#x2019;d given it a better chance. It&#x2019;s like a jigsaw puzzle with strange rules. See that picture? That&#x2019;s chlorophyll. Check out that magnesium nitrogen structure in the middle. How cool is that?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For some reason, most of the stories that come into mind involve fields of science other than electrical and computer engineering. You know, the field I&#x2019;d actually be able to write about without doing research. I suppose I should be happy to have reasons to be learning new things, but it&#x2019;s pretty irritating to sit down to write a story and have to stop every few paragraphs to look up things like the chemical composition of chlorophyll. I think what this means, is I actually need friends in each field of science that I can bounce ideas off of, instead of actually trying to figure this stuff out myself. Anyone out there a chemist?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/2/5_Why_didnt_I_pay_more_attention_in_school.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/1/21_Baby.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6134116c-b8e9-405d-867b-2f3cb85e5d7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 20:43:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>You know how they say the instant you hold your child in your arms for the first time your life changes? Well...maybe the second time. The first time I was so out of it and overwhelmed, it didn&#x2019;t really occur to me that this was my child that some kind nurse had put into my exhausted arms and was still kind of holding in case I wasn&#x2019;t up to the task. It was more like: Oh look, a baby. Well isn&#x2019;t that nice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Second time? Bam. Nothing can prepare you for the sudden feeling that you would claw the face off of anyone who even suggests that your child is not the most adorable thing in the world. It&#x2019;s quite powerful and pretty surreal.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;See that bandage on the back of my hand? It&#x2019;s one of 8 places I got stuck with a needle over the course of about 4 days. My veins are troublesome for people in the blood drawing business. More so when I haven&#x2019;t been allowed to drink water for 14 hours. So let&#x2019;s back up 14 hours...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;January the 14th&lt;br/&gt;4:20am. I&#x2019;m awoken by the feeling of fluid pouring from between my legs. Rush to the bathroom faster than I&#x2019;ve been able to walk in the past few months due to a large abdomen. Good thing amniotic fluid doesn&#x2019;t stain carpet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4:21am. Sean? Call the doctor, I think my water broke. This is too soon. Wow, that&#x2019;s a lot of fluid.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4:25am. Wait, I can&#x2019;t pack a bag? We have to go to the hospital right this second? Oh, alright. I guess that&#x2019;s okay.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4:45am. Well I&#x2019;m glad that second gush of amniotic fluid waited until I got out of the car to arrive. Wow, my pants are soaked. This is awkward. I hope they don&#x2019;t mind I&#x2019;m dripping in their hallway.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;5:00am. I&#x2019;m having a contraction? Huh. Don&#x2019;t feel anything. Why is the doctor startled by the amount of fluid coming out of me?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;5:30am. Well this is a nicer room than triage. But I&#x2019;m stuck in bed from now until the baby comes? And you&#x2019;re hoping for two weeks?! Damn. Ooh, ice chips.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;7:00am. This magnesium sulfate stuff stinks. I&#x2019;m so freaking hot. Isn&#x2019;t this just epsom salt? At least I&#x2019;m not vomiting like my sister did. Ooh, ice chips.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;7:10am. You&#x2019;re sticking that needle of steroids where? Son of a -! Ooh, ice chips.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;7:20am. Hello sonogram technician. You don&#x2019;t need to explain this to me, I&#x2019;ve have like a dozen of these. Yes yes, there&#x2019;s his head and his heart. Very cool. You&#x2019;re keeping me from my ice chips. My amniotic fluid level is normal? Really, cause I swear I&#x2019;ve lost like a gallon. Come to think of it, my abdomen feels a lot better now.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;8:00am. Thank you for turning down the magnesium, I&#x2019;m feeling much better now. So...I guess I sleep for about 23 hours now? Just a few more ice chips for the road.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;9:00am. Drowsy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;10:00am. Drowsy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;11:00am. Drowsy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;12:00pm. Ice chips.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1:00pm. Drowsy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2:00pm. Drowsy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3:00pm. Blood work eh? Good luck with that. Take two? Okay, but that seems like a strange spot to try and get blood. Bloody hell it hurts when you wiggle it around like that.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3:10pm. Okay, second tech. Seriously? Two of you can&#x2019;t get blood out of me? Well why the heck didn&#x2019;t you prick my finger and squeeze blood out after the first failed attempt?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4:00pm. Shouldn&#x2019;t my contractions be getting further apart instead of closer together? Damn, up with the magnesium again?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;5:00pm. Hey, these are getting pretty frequent. And kind of uncomfortable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;6:00pm. Okay, these kind of hurt. Can you get a doctor in here?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;6:30pm. Okay, I really need a doctor. These ice chips are doing nothing for me anymore. And something&#x2019;s trying to leave my body.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;6:35pm. Doctor! Finally! Pain! No drugs? Crowning? What?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;6:45pm. Whew, I&#x2019;m beat. Wait, what the hell just happened? Where are my ice chips? What&#x2019;s that crying? What&#x2019;s the big bloody bag looking thing you put in that big tupperware container? Hey, those stitches you&#x2019;re putting in kind of hurt, can I get some drugs now? Wow, look at all that blood. Oh look, a baby. Well isn&#x2019;t that nice. Can I have some more ice chips?&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/1/21_Baby.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Contest!</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/12/19_Book_Contest%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002ff14a-f160-4141-9735-200733d48359</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 10:09:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&#x201D;The Children of Doctor Lancing&#x201D; is finally published! Special thanks to everyone who helped it along.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Are you interested in having a character in the next book named after you? Here&#x2019;s how to be entered in a random drawing for your name to be used:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Between now and May, when you write a review of either of my books to post on Amazon, &lt;a href="mailto:michelleamcbeth@gmail.com?subject=review%20contest/"&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt; a copy of your review before you submit it. Along with your review, let me know how you would like your name to appear in print. That&#x2019;s it!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The longer your review, the higher the chances are that your name will get drawn. So try to be more specific than just saying &#x201C;I loved it!&#x201D;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Remember, you can write a review for either &#x201C;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00RM1MMDS?*Version*=1&amp;*entries*=0"&gt;The Sphere&lt;/a&gt;&#x201D; or &#x201C;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B019CH8CYC?*Version*=1&amp;*entries*=0"&gt;The Children of Doctor Lancing&lt;/a&gt;&#x201D;, and if you write one for each, your chances of being picked are even greater. Make sure you email it to me before it goes live, so I know for sure that it&#x2019;s your review. Good luck!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/12/19_Book_Contest%21.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
