<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ramblings</title>
    <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description> </description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Blog_files/DSC_0101.jpg</url>
      <title>Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Scout Results</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/8/6_Kindle_Scout_Results.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc36a7a-c1c7-4025-9e81-fa66ace647ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2017 07:50:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;So I didn’t win again, but I got a fair amount out of my campaign. For one thing, I did get a few people interested enough in my series to buy my first book. Here’s hoping for some good reviews.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I’m pleased that I wasn’t immediately rejected. Last time I got my no-thank-you notice in about three days. This time it was almost two weeks. I’d like to think that they were seriously considering it and not just all on vacation. Since I’ll never know for sure, I choose to believe the former.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I got about three times the page hits of my first campaign and an overwhelming 92% of those were people who simply found my book on KS and checked it out. Only 8% were people I sent the direct link to, begging for votes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As I suspected, by biggest hits were the last few days of my campaign. That seems to be the case with the hot &amp;amp; trending list as well-books that are about to end their campaigns are the majority of the list. It makes sense, since you only get three votes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I can’t bring myself to be too disappointed. I’m apparently not the target audience of most scouters, and to be honest, some of the books that get selected look pretty crappy. I understand KS does put you through a round or two of professional editing, but I guess if you’re starting from 50 Shades, it’s hard to improve to Scarlet Letter.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Oh well! Look for “The Lunar Conspiracy” in late August, 2017!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Panel</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/7/23_Author_Panel.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b76b8acd-666e-4906-a82b-d1491e95427b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 08:48:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>A few weeks ago I participated in an author panel hosted by the Northern Virginia Writer’s Club about “Pathways to Publishing”. See me on the right there? I’m sitting next to several authors who have been published through the traditional route.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I was a little nervous since this is the first panel of this type I’ve ever participated in, but it went well. I got a few laughs. We had a bigger audience than we had anticipated, and many people came up after to tell us how informative it had been. It was also interesting for me to sit up there and listen to authors who have gone the traditional route talk about the pros and cons. Some of the authors have gone both routes. It seems like the biggest comment on the differences is that self-publishing just means a lot more work on your part.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I had fun, and the club got a few new members and I hope we inspired some people to take the plunge and work on getting that book they’ve had sitting around on their laptop for years finally published! If you’re a writer in Norther Virginia or just Virginia, take a look at the websites for the Virginia Writer’s Club and our local chapter. They host lots of fun and informative events.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Virginia Writer’s Club:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.virginiawritersclub.org/&quot;&gt;http://www.virginiawritersclub.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Northern Virginia Writer’s Club:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://northernvirginiawriters.org/&quot;&gt;http://northernvirginiawriters.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Scout Take 2</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2017/6/24_Kindle_Scout_Take_2.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b947b18-73c1-4ecf-9327-b4fba1161d8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 07:24:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;br/&gt;Although “The Sphere” wasn’t selected for publication by Kindle Scout, I am not discouraged by the idea of trying again. For one thing, my writing has improved greatly. For another, I now have three books in my series. Even if “The Lunar Conspiracy” isn’t chosen either, I expect I’ll see an uptick in sales from people who read the excerpt and are intrigued enough to go look at the first two books. And if I’m not chosen, I can still publish on my own. Seems like a win-win.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A number of things have changed since my first try at Kindle Scout. For one thing, Amazon now provides you with daily page hits, so you can see how your book is doing. On day one, 326 people looked at my book. Unfortunately, they don’t tell you how many of those people nominated your book. Bear in mind though, I haven’t even started my social media push. Those are overwhelmingly people who were already on Kindle Scout, saw my book and decided to take a look at it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is one of the reasons why a good cover is so important. It’s shallow, but the adage is true: People judge a book by its cover. So those books on Scout that are very obviously some clip art and basic fonts thrown onto a picture the author took themselves? I admit, I don’t bother looking at them. I might be missing out on an awesome book, but it shows a lack of effort I just can’t get past. Same thing if there are typos on the campaign page; of which I pray I don’t have any.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As a scouter, there is also an advantage to waiting to nominate a book until it is close to ending. I’d guess on average amazon adds five books a day, which means every day an average of five books are removed and weighed for publication. Every day you could nominate three out of those five books and possibly get three free books a day out of it! I haven’t tested this theory, but it seems possible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And this is all free publicity for Amazon. They’re making out big time with increased traffic to their websites and books they publish, or even books that end up self-publishing later. Amazon will now send an email to everyone who nominated your book when you publish it (if outside of Scout). It seems like a really sweet thing of them to do, until you realize that the majority of the proceeds from those sales goes directly to them. It’s a pretty brilliant if shallow business model.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Judging from the books that tend to end up on the “hot and trending” list, it’s clear my next book needs to be about a hot teenage vampire that falls in love with a hot teenage werewolf and has a love child that turns into a hot sorceress who travels through time seducing really hot young versions of famous men. The cover needs to feature at least two of these hot people showing lots of skin and contemplative faces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I’m copyrighting that idea, so no one better steal it!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaithersburg</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/3/26_Gaithersburg.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58242a3f-2d08-4962-93a9-b1e0bfc6a5cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 08:14:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Yesterday was the Gaithersburg Book Festival. I was really pleased to get a spot again this year since it went so well for me last year. Even with the horrid weather and an infant in tow, it was a good time. I met some very nice people and got a few questions that really challenged me. I also have to thank my mother-in-law (back there with Sheffield) for helping out yesterday, and my husband (taking the selfie) for his awesome sales work. Though the tactic of yelling “Time Travel” at people walking by seemed to startle them more than get them to stop at the table.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On the right there is the concept of the cover for book number 3 in The Sphere Saga, tentatively titled “The Lunar Conspiracy”. Since so many people purchased copies of my books yesterday, I’m going to extend the character name contest out a few more months. So if you read one of my books and &lt;a href=&quot;Entries/2015/12/19_Book_Contest%21.html&quot;&gt;write a review&lt;/a&gt; before September, let me know!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloopers</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2016/2/21_Bloopers.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82a5e2d9-7bfd-4929-a894-0cffe28d4d61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 09:15:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>To the left is a snapshot from The Washington Post online newspaper the other day. See that picture with the pope? That’s what they ran on the front page with that headline about sharks. If you clicked on it, the article was actually about the sharks, but I found the mistake amusing. The appalling thing is the regularity with which these sorts of mistakes happen. In The Washington Post. A national newspaper.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You paying attention Bezos? The other thing that has started to annoy me about Wapo articles is the number of times you’ll go to read an article and in the middle of it are snapshots of what people on twitter are saying about something that happened. Is this what qualifies as journalism now? I went on twitter and copied the most liked comments for a specific hashtag? If I wanted to read twitter comments, I would be on the twitter. I don’t need you to do it for me, “journalist”.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Why do I get the impression that this is actually a decree that came down from up high? I could totally imagine Bezos saying to the top editors (or whatever equivalent power structure), “We need to incorporate more social media in our newspaper!” Or whatever management buzzwordy way he would say it. Slowly, Wapo will transform itself from an actual newspaper to the facebook of journalism, and we’ll be reading stories about what’s for sale on Amazon that day. I fear the future. Even if I shop on Amazon almost every day. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
