<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ramblings</title>
    <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description> </description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Blog_files/DSC_0101.jpg</url>
      <title>Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Worlds Collide</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/5/24_Worlds_Collide.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc9705e-927c-48be-88c3-eedd724156cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/5/24_Worlds_Collide_files/IMAG0643%20%281%29.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Media/object014_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:107px; height:155px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;My day job (the one that actually makes me money) is as an electrical engineer. Day to day, I write programs, design embedded systems, run field tests and such. Sometimes I have to purchase equipment from companies. I recently had a rather pleasant and lengthy email exchange with one such company, when I purchased one of their boards and had to exchange it for another (my own fault, not theirs). While nailing down the details for the exchange, their lovely salesperson mentioned finding a book called “The Sphere” on Amazon, and wondered if I was the same Michelle McBeth. Indeed I was! They were very excited by the summary of it, and downloaded it that very day.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I found the whole thing exciting and just a little unsettling. I consider my book to be part of my personal life, and I tend to keep my personal life rather separate from my work. It’s part of the reason no coworker has ever seen me in a play, and probably never will. It’s also why I haven’t talked about my book much at work. Very few people at this point even know about it. It’s the opposite of good marketing tactics.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I assume this hesitation on my part has to do with a desire to keep a professional impression of myself upon the people I work with. I’ve always been very reserved with my emotions, and acting and writing this book definitely breech that boundary. The book a little less so than acting. My father recently commented that he couldn’t read my book without picturing me as Adelaide. It makes sense, since the character is slightly autobiographical. Then I realized it’s a good thing my sister Heather’s book is geared towards teens. I can’t imagine what my father would think reading the end of “The Ghost in my Bedroom” and picturing her. The end of the book was disturbing and upsetting. Frankly, I cried, because I couldn’t help but not picture my sister. In that sense, I think she is incredibly brave in her story choices.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The idea of one day being famous terrifies me. It’s strange, since I’m perfectly comfortable performing in front of people (normal stage jitters aside). In grad school I became very adept at giving presentations on my research, and know how to work a room very well. But in both of these situations, it’s not me. It’s my work personae. It’s the character I’m playing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And it’s exhausting.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/5/24_Worlds_Collide_files/IMAG0643%20%281%29.jpg" length="129680" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Fair Results</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/3/27_Book_Fair_Results.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c55f33c-6a04-4d79-a116-17f318740e9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2015 11:12:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/3/27_Book_Fair_Results_files/20150321_132540.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Media/object001_4.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:118px; height:175px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;This past weekend Sean and I traveled to Charlottesville, VA for their annual book fair. I had a table in the hotel lobby with many other authors and writing related companies. It was quite a learning experience.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The biggest problem is getting people to figure out what you're all about in about a 2 second glance. My book covers don't necessarily inflict &amp;quot;sci-fi&amp;quot; into people's minds, even with the starry background and distinctly tech looking wireframe objects. About 10 minutes after setting up our table, Sean made a small sign that said &amp;quot;sci-fi&amp;quot;. It caught the attention of a few people (&amp;quot;Ooh, sic-fi!&amp;quot;) but for the most part we still had to try and engage the person as they walked by:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;Hello! Do you like sci-fi?&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;No, sorry.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;No, but my grandson does.&amp;quot; (Got that one quite often. Apparently Charlottesville is full of older women with techy grandsons.) &amp;quot;I can't even figure out my TV.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Yes!&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Aha! My target audience! All 20 of them!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For the amount of people who actually stopped at my table to talk and find out more about the book, I'd say 30% purchased a book. Of those who didn't, a few took cards to check out my website later, or &lt;a href=&quot;Entries/2015/3/27_Book_Fair_Results_files/newsletter_signup.html&quot;&gt;signed up for my monthly newsletter&lt;/a&gt;. A bunch of people had freebies to lure folks in. I'm not a fan of freebies, since I've been to plenty a convention where people just scout tables for free stuff with no intention of engaging any of the vendors. However I do think giving something away with any book purchase is a smart idea. Sean and I were toying with a logo for Lancing Electronics that we could turn into mugs and such. I'm not a fan of taking your book cover and merely slapping it on merchandise. I don't think I've ever seen a book cover that would itself well to that sort of object. The sole exception perhaps being &amp;quot;Hitchhiker's Guide To the Galaxy&amp;quot;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Another idea we had was doing a dramatic interpretation of my book every half hour or so. It would seriously be hilarious.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So to summarize what I learned:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Find some way to grab people's attention.&lt;br/&gt;2. Find ways to reach a more targeted audience.&lt;br/&gt;3. Free stuff!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All in all, it was a great experience, and probably a good starter for me.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/3/27_Book_Fair_Results_files/20150321_132540.jpg" length="140689" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Fair</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/3/20_Book_Fair.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a146510-3a8e-4f4c-b312-dfb0e9b145ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 10:28:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/3/20_Book_Fair_files/lancing-poster2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Media/object004_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:120px; height:175px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Some exciting news! Tomorrow I will be participating in my first book fair. It’s taking place in the Omni Hotel in Charlottesville, VA. I have a table and copies of my book and business cards and everything. It’s almost like I’m a professional!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Sean has produced the first version of my cover, as you can see to the left. We’re sticking with the sphere and wireframe against a starry background theme. The finished version will be very similar. The “Fall 2015” banner will be gone. And there will be a back side. But otherwise, it’s basically the same. Maybe some tweaking of the lights. Maybe not. Probably not. I mean, you can tell it’s a hand, right? Maybe.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In other exciting news, I left my book on the shelf of a local coffeehouse and someone has taken it. I hope to read it, and not use it for kindling or something. And person, if you’ve found your way to this page from the link on the back cover, Hi! And if you enjoyed it, please leave me a review on Amazon: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00RM1MMDS&quot;&gt;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00RM1MMDS&lt;/a&gt;   And if you hated it, I’m sorry, and the next book will be better. I promise. It made me cry. For good reasons.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Speaking of that. The first draft is out for feedback! Work is moving along, so I’m hopeful that Fall 2015 banner will not be a lie. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/3/20_Book_Fair_files/lancing-poster2.jpg" length="223080" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glowing Eyes</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/2/16_Glowing_Eyes.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e21104a2-c2a8-4b20-8092-333d074e753e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 14:02:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/2/16_Glowing_Eyes_files/IMG_20150216_135431_478.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Media/object000_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:108px; height:111px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I’m a bad author that hasn’t written to her blog in...apparently 6 weeks. But I had a project I’ve been working on, that I wanted to post about!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A few weeks ago I was cast as the ghost in Port City Playhouse’s production of “Shining City” by Connor McPherson. It’s a non-speaking role and most of my acting is through pictures that will be displayed, but I will appear on stage briefly, as the ghost.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The director of the show was thinking it would be neat if they could find a way to get my eyes to glow red, and turns to me and says: Well you’re an electrical engineer, can you find a way to make that happen?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Of course! A couple of ping pong balls, felt, glue, high intensity LEDs and basic electronics later and I’ve got a couple of working prototype eyes. I took them in to get a feel for which style the director liked better, then set to work putting them both into a more permanent arrangement with an on/off switch.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So a few night ago I’ve finally got the thing soldered together and am getting ready to cover the solder joints with heat shrink tubing to smooth them out and make me less prone to shorting something out with my wet hair (part of the costume). I don’t have a heat gun at home, but Sean suggests using the soldering iron held close to the tube but not touching. It’s working, but very very slowly, and I’m impatient. So next he suggests holding a lighter up to the tube to make faster work of shrinking them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Great idea! Except that a slice of ping pong ball that’s been slathered with glue and lined with felt is highly flammable.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Well, I wasn’t liking how that LED was seated anyway, so now I have a valid reason to re-do that eye. Take two; I’m being patient and using the soldering iron for the joints near the eyeballs, at short intervals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The final product is feeling much better. The LEDs are solidly mounted and not likely to be shifting around on me. The wiring is cleaner. There will probably be some color changes once we figure out if I’m wearing these with my glasses or not. But on the whole, it’s done! Enjoy &lt;a href=&quot;../My_Albums/Pages/Eye_Photos.html&quot;&gt;pictures&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2015/2/16_Glowing_Eyes_files/IMG_20150216_135431_478.jpg" length="90953" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“The Sphere” is out!</title>
      <link>http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2014/12/31_The_Sphere_is_out%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d380a3b-abbb-40df-b29f-67c80ab93eaa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 11:01:01 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2014/12/31_The_Sphere_is_out%21_files/cover.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Media/object001_4.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:107px; height:150px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Like I promised, “The Sphere” has now been published on CreateSpace and Amazon Kindle Direct. The books are not yet linked together, so there are technically two versions. I hear that should be fixed in about a week.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ebook: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/The-Sphere-Journey-In-Time-ebook/dp/B00RM1MMDS/ref=pd_rhf_gw_p_img_1&quot;&gt;http://www.amazon.com/The-Sphere-Journey-In-Time-ebook/dp/B00RM1MMDS/ref=pd_rhf_gw_p_img_1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Print version (soon on amazon): &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.createspace.com/5179486&quot;&gt;https://www.createspace.com/5179486&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A great new book for the new year!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://michellemcbeth.com/michellemcbeth.com/Blog/Entries/2014/12/31_The_Sphere_is_out%21_files/cover.jpg" length="212375" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
