<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="6FC2B3E7-67AD-4FEB-B35E-19203ADD6156">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20170723" date="2017-07-23 13:00:40 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Michelle McBeth</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>A few weeks ago I participated in an author panel hosted by the Northern Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club about &#x201C;Pathways to Publishing&#x201D;. See me on the right there? I&#x2019;m sitting next to several authors who have been published through the traditional route.&#xD;&#xD;I was a little nervous since this is the first panel of this type I&#x2019;ve ever participated in, but it went well. I got a few laughs. We had a bigger audience than we had anticipated, and many people came up after to tell us how informative it had been. It was also interesting for me to sit up there and listen to authors who have gone the traditional route talk about the pros and cons. Some of the authors have gone both routes. It seems like the biggest comment on the differences is that self-publishing just means a lot more work on your part.&#xD;&#xD;I had fun, and the club got a few new members and I hope we inspired some people to take the plunge and work on getting that book they&#x2019;ve had sitting around on their laptop for years finally published! If you&#x2019;re a writer in Norther Virginia or just Virginia, take a look at the websites for the Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club and our local chapter. They host lots of fun and informative events.&#xD;&#xD;Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club:&#xD;&lt;a href="http://www.virginiawritersclub.org/"&gt;http://www.virginiawritersclub.org/&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;Northern Virginia Writer&#x2019;s Club:&#xD;&lt;a href="http://northernvirginiawriters.org/"&gt;http://northernvirginiawriters.org/&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, July 23, 2017&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Author Panel</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
