<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="6FC2B3E7-67AD-4FEB-B35E-19203ADD6156">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20170319" date="2017-03-19 15:02:22 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Michelle McBeth</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>One of the questions I get at book fairs that I struggle with the most is "Who are your favorite authors?" I think it's partly because my mind is so focused on the specifics of my book at that point, it's hard to cast it about for things I've recently read and really enjoyed. Also, I don't read much hard-core science fiction, and I figure that's what people are expecting. Also, I just don't read that much any more, which is probably a horrible thing for an author to admit. In talking with another sci-fi writer at a recent book fair, he dropped the names of a bunch of sci-fi authors who I had never even heard of, and it made me feel inferior. Like I wasn't doing my part to further the work of other lesser known writers.&#xD;&#xD;One of my favorite authors has been Michael Crichton. I appreciate how much effort and research he puts into his books while still keeping you on the edge of your seat. I tore through Jurassic Park in about two days when I was in grade school, and learned quite a bit in reading it. I have since read a half dozen or so of his books, including "State of Fear", which I just finished.&#xD;&#xD;"State of Fear" was a really interesting book, though I fear most people simply dismiss it as being some sort of anti global warming propaganda. It is indeed about a group of people trying to stage several global catastrophes coinciding with a conference on sudden climate change. The idea being that it will generate a ton of publicity and money for the cause to fight global warming. Most importantly, it feeds the media's top tool in getting us to pay attention: fear.&#xD;&#xD;This idea is important, and real. I think some of the more respectable news sources are starting to back off from the idea, but there's still plenty of click-bait headlines out there. Just the other day, there was an article in the Washington Post titled "The strange star that has serious scientists talking about an alien megastructure." The article is also accompanied by a strange looking rock shape that's actually the ruins of an ancient church taken as a long exposure during a meteor shower. When you go on to read the article, it mentions that the strange light pattern is hard to explain, but that there's an extremely remote possibility it could be caused by a structure built by aliens, assuming all natural causes are ruled out. Not nearly as exciting as photographic evidence of a strange alien megastructure.&#xD;&#xD;Hey, didn't you hear? Bacon causes cancer, and coffee is once again good for you.&#xD;&#xD;The bigger takeaway from the book is just to be skeptical about what you read. There's plenty of scientific data out there that counters the global warming argument-why do you never hear about that? Instead of ignoring it, perhaps scientists should explain why it doesn't matter instead of focusing on convenient truths. Then maybe I'll start trusting you.&#xD;&#xD;I believe the end result is still a good one, I just don't want to be lied to about it. I still recycle, drive a low-emission vehicle and support the idea of clean air power. But forget solar and wind. Power beaming is the future!&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, November 4, 2015&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Recent Read</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
